

Profile

I am an expert in Web development and Blockchain.

From 2015 I have worked in the famous software companies as **Blockchain** developer, Software engineer, Project manager.

I provide my customers with the perfect **front end** and **back end** in which **strong fashion** and **business style**, **gorgeousness** and **delicacy** are in harmony.

I have built so much project for that time and I would introduce it here.

- thunderpick.com (Cryptocurrency betting site)
- chainguardians.io (Cryptocurrency betting site)
- getmyboat.com (World boat booking site)
- ethereummax.org (DEX)
- airbnb.com (Booking site)

My latest company was **NipponFWD** in Japan and there my role was:

- Blockchain developer
- Project Manager

There I built more **smart contracts** using **ERC-20** and **ERC-721** custom tokens which will work on Ethereum, Binance Smart Chain and I was reponsible for building **NFT Marketplace** and created custom tokens using **openzepplin**, implemented **MetaMask**, **Torus** and **other wallets** to increase user experience.

Employment History

Full-stack developer, 4K-Soft, Kyiv

SEPTEMBER 2015 - JUNE 2017

I have worked as Full-stact developer in this company.

Have been working with Javascript frameworks, PHP frameworks, Database platforms, CSS frameworks, CMS for years, and have many projects where I played as a main developer.

Project manger, Blockchain Developer, NipponFWD, Tokyo

JULY 2017 - JUNE 2021

I have rich experiences of building **smart contracts** for a lot of projects on various blockchain networks such as **Ethereum**, **Binance Smart Cchain**, **polygon**, **Alorand**, **Solona**. etc.

Especially so far I have mostly kept on **NFT crypto space** like several kinds of games and **NFT marketplace** platforms using **openzepplin** ERC token standards like **ERC-20**, **ERC-721**, **ERC-1155** tokens you know.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science, The University of Tokyo, Tokyo

JULY 2012 - JUNE 2015

- Majoring in Computer Science and Technology.
- Top marks in all subjects.

Details

bigstarcoolmanager@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Japanese-Russian

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

1995-05-05

Tokvo

Skills

Solidity

Web3.js

Rust

Pyteal

Git

React

Node.js

DevOps

Vue.js

Angular.js

Tailwind CSS

Bootstrap

Laravel

Database Management

Links

My Portfolio

My Github

Languages

English

Hobbies

Sports, Singing.